Fuck Wolverine.
First, he rides my coattails
with the R rating.
Then the hairy motherfucker
ups the ante by dying.
What a dick.
Well, guess what, Wolvie?
I'm dying in this one, too.
To understand why
I took a cat-nap
on 1,200 gallons of
high-test fuel...
I need to take you back
to the dewy slopes
of six weeks ago.
I'd gone international,
taking out mass
murderers, gangsters,
unspeakable monsters.
People nobody would touch.
Except me.
I'm gonna touch them all over.
Hey, it's Gail calling.
Love the shiny suit.
Really brings out
the sex trafficker in your eyes.
I don't speak
Cantonese, Mister...
Well, I'm not even
gonna attempt that.
But I did take 8th
grade Spanish, so...
Which literally translates to...
I don't bargain, pumpkin fucker.
Oh. Oh, this isn't Gilbert's.
I am so sorry.
I thought this was an
anal-bleaching party.
Don't worry. You're
not going to die.
Although these will kill you.
Hit it, Dolly.
I'm merely a vessel
for the Lord.
Taking the hands out of the
guns of the criminals!
Whoo! Do not go in there!
Let's see Captain
America do that.
Too exotic?
Oh, God! Oh, God, time out!
Time out!
Cut. I've got bad guy blood,
right in my open eye.
Oh, that's so gross.
Fuck.
Looks like you left a
little landing strip there.
I like it.
Oh, man!
My world tour brought me home
to this guy, Sergei Valishnikov.
But we'll get to
him in a moment.
'Cause I know what
you're thinking.
"I'm so glad I left
the kiddos at home."
But that's where you'd be wrong.
That babysitter of yours is
high as fuck right now...
and, believe it or not,
Deadpool 2 is a family film.
True story.
And every good family film
starts with a vicious murder.
Bambi, The Lion King, Saw 7.
Holy shit pickles!
That guy's on fire.
That's not CGI, folks.
He's actually on fire.
Yeah. You know I get paid to
take out bad guys, right?
But this guy?
He was one of the worst of 'em.
Hurry up and open
this fucking door,
and let's kill
this motherfucker!
Ugh. So gross.
A panic room? Really?
Can you come out?
I really have to go.
It's my anniversary.
Over and over, I
hear people say,
"I just don't have
enough confidence."
Listen, confidence is
not something you have.
It's something you create.
And you can create it
at any moment in time.
A sense of confidence is nothing
but a sense of power
within yourself...
a sense of certainty that
you can pull something off.
Start the fucking car!
Dopinder!
Shoot that motherfucker!
Shoot him!
Whoo! Oh, I shit my pants.
Actually, that may have been me.
Oh, mission accomplished?
Oh, in a George W. Sort of way.
Fucker can't stay in a
panic room forever.
Oh, you're living
the dreams, DP.
It has been quite
the run, Dopinder,
and who'da thought?
Now I'm talked about in the
same sentence as Jesus.
Passion of the Christ, then me.
At least domestically.
We beat them overseas,
where there's no such
thing as religion.
I do want to live the
dreams, Pool Boy.
Taxiing is not as
sexy as it looks.
I want to fill my... Pockets?
What's your poison? A
little, uh, cokey cokey?
Can't maintain an erection
without buying shoes online?
I've never experienced
that last one.
Talk to me, Goose.
I was going to say "soul".
I want to fill my soul.
I want to belong to something,
like you, Pool, sir.
Dopinder... Hmm?
You never cease to surprise me.
You know, the depth of your
heart is extraordinary.
We all need a sense
of belonging.
We all need a genuine
sense of home.
A place in this world.
I want to become a
contract killer.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
Remember when I kidnapped Bandhu
and threatened him
with great violence?
You kind of killed him.
And then remember the movie
Interview with the Vampire?
Don't want to.
When Tom Cruise fed
10-year-old Kirsten Dunst blood
for the first time...
and she looked up at his smooth,
handsome face and said...
"I want some more."
Oh, Pool, picture me, a
10-year-old Kirsten Dunst.
I'll never not picture that.
But I can't wait to
never speak of this,
as soon as possible.
We're here.
Dopinder, it's me again.
Look, a saner man
might discourage you
from joining the deadly
merc business...
what, with your concave chest
and your paper towel tube arms.
But you're an eagle...
and goddamn it, an
eagle's gotta soar.
You gotta grab those dreams,
grab those dreams
by the dick tip...
and make it rain!
I don't know what that means.
Me neither.
I'm gonna see you...
at the office.
In the sky.
You're my Tom Cruise!
And you're my Kristen Dunst!
Kristen? Kirsten?
Sorry I'm late.
There was a bunch of
handicapable children
stuck in a tree...
and I had to, uh... Uh-uh.
You're right. I was
fighting a caped badass.
But then we discovered his
mom is named Martha, too.
No.You got me.
I was rounding up all
the gluten in the world
and launching it into space...
where it can't not
hurt us ever again.
Try again.
Diarrhea?
We can't be sure until
I get this suit off...
but, uh, all signs point to yes.
Traffic?
Hmm?
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
Well, come here.
I'm gonna shower and
get out of this suit.
Don't you want your surprise?
Do I look like a
patient burn victim?
I got one for you, too.
Happy anniversary, baby.
Open, open, open.
Skee-Ball token.
Our first date.
Yup.
That's genuine, high-grade lead.
I'll keep it forever.
Thank you, baby.
Open yours. All
right, all right.
Oh...
That's just the most
beautiful thing that I've...
I don't know what this is.
My IUD.
A bomb?
No, dick for brains. My
birth control device.
What, you mean that your...
Baby factory's
open for business.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I want a boy!
Or a little girl! Definitely
one or the other!
Oh! And I want our kid
to have only one name.
Like Cher or Todd.
You gotta pump a baby
in me first, cowboy.
Yes, I do.
Let's watch some porn and
show that bed who's boss.
Let's do that.
♪ Papa... ♪
♪ Can you hear me? ♪
♪ Papa, can you see me? ♪
Does this song sound
familiar to you?
May.
Connor, if it's a boy.
May, if it's a girl.
So weird.
Family was always
an F-word to me.
My pile of shit father
took off and bailed.
I mean, it's not like I have
a lot of strong role models
to draw off of for Todd.
Hey. Look at me.
You are not your father.
Besides...
I will never, ever let
our child be named Todd.
But here's the thing,
isn't that how it always works?
Like in Star Wars,
men are destined to
become their father...
and then have consensual
sex with their sister?
I think you missed big,
big chunks of that movie.
No, I'm pretty sure
Luke nailed her.
Baby, that's Empire.
The point is, kids...
they give us a chance to
be better than we are.
Better than we used to be.
You're a lot smarter
than I look.
I'm gonna go make dessert.
You get the strap-on.
Let's make a super baby.
Pretty sure it doesn't work
that way, but we can try.
What about Krystal?
But with a "K"?
It's too stripper-y.
Kevin with a "K"!
No, too stripper-y, too.
Uh, Earl!
He's gonna go straight to jail
if we name him Earl.
What about Bruce?
No.
Get down.
What?
Baby? Baby?
I'm okay.
Thank God I didn't have to use
the cream cheese spreader.
Please.
Please. Please.
Baby, I'm so sorry.
No!
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
Is it just me, or does
Do You Want to Build a Snowman?
from Frozen...
sound suspiciously like
Papa, Can You Hear Me?
From Yentl?
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
And nobody fucking realizes it.
Wade, you gotta go home.
You've been sitting here
for three days, okay?
You smell like sauerkraut
left in the warm rain.
Like wet garbage in hot urine.
You smell like a dog
ate kitty litter...
and then farted his way
out of the living room.